mobileroadie.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy - Mobile Roadie App Maker

_Last modified: 25 May 2018_

Mobile Roadie, Inc. (“Mobile Roadie”, “we” or “us”) provides a platform to enable customers (“Mobile Roadie Customers”) to develop and manage smart phone and tablet applications (each a “Mobile Application”) and mobile website solutions (each a “Mobile Site”) as well as related hosting and support services (the "Service"). As used in this document “Mobile Offering” means the Mobile Applications and Mobile Sites. 

This Privacy Policy is made available on our website at https://mobileroadie.com/privacy (“Site”), and provides information on our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from (i) Mobile Roadie Customers, (ii) end users that download, access and/or use the Mobile Offerings (“End Users”), and (iii) visitors just browsing the Site (“Visitors”). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. 

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally. 

Mobile Roadie cares about your privacy. For this reason, we only collect and use personal data as needed to fully deliver our services to you. Your personal data includes information such as: 

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Telephone number 
  * Date of birth 
  * Email address 
  * Other data collected that could directly or indirectly identify you. 

Our Privacy Policy is intended to describe how we collect data, what exactly is collected, how we use this personal data, and why it is used. It also describes options we provide for you to access, update or otherwise take control of your personal data that we process. 

If at any time you have questions about our practices or any of your rights described below, you may reach our dedicated team by contacting us at [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com). This inbox is actively monitored and managed so that we can deliver an experience that you can confidently trust. 

## (A) Mobile Roadie Customers

**What personal information do we collect?**

If you are a Mobile Roadie Customer, when you register with us through the Site to create and manage Mobile Offerings, we will ask you for personally identifiable information, such as your full name, company name, email address, billing address, phone, payment information. 

In addition, we may collect information related to interactions of End Users with your Mobile Offerings as described in part (B) below. 

**How we use your personal data?**

We use such personally identifiable information (in some cases, in conjunction with your non-identifying information, such as your zip code) mainly to provide the Mobile Roadie services, register you as customer for mobile offering creation and management, complete your transactions, administer your inquiries, and contact Mobile Roadie Customers regarding account activities, new version and product offerings, or other communications relevant to the Mobile Roadie services. 

We do not sell any personally identifiable information of Mobile Roadie Customers to any third parties. The instances where we may share such information with third parties are described in part (D) below. 

**How you can access, update or delete your data?**

You may review and update the personally identifiable information in your registration profile by logging in and editing such information in your dashboard. If you decide to delete all of your personal information we may cancel your account. You can also send a request to [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com) to initiate the removal of your personal data. The request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements. 

Also, you have the right to receive a copy of certain personal information we process about you. This comprises any personal information we process on the basis of your consent. You have the right to receive this information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. You also have the right to request that we transfer that personal information to another party. You may contact us at [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com) to initiate the preparation process of a copy of your personal data. 

If you wish for us to transfer such personal information to a third party, please ensure you detail that party in your request. Note that we can only do so where it is technically feasible. Please note that we may not be able to provide you with personal information if providing it would interfere with another's rights (e.g., where providing the personal information we hold about you would reveal information about another person or our trade secrets or intellectual property). 

## (B) End Users

**What personal information do we collect?**

Except in the case of Free Mobile Website Solutions (defined below), if you decide to download, access and/or use a Mobile Offering, we will be collecting and storing on behalf of the applicable Mobile Roadie Customer any personally identifiable information that you provide to such Mobile Roadie Customer. This information may include your full name, email address, postal code, birthday and gender. Some data is optional information that a Mobile Roadie Customer may choose to collect, which optional information and is not required to use the Mobile Offering. Other instances where the data you provide through use of a Mobile Offering is collected by Mobile Roadie on behalf of our Customers is where you choose to allow a Mobile Offering to collect your location data. In these instances such location data will be available to the applicable Mobile Roadie Customer. 

In addition, if you have an account with Facebook, Twitter, or Foursquare or other similar websites (each a “Social Network”), your Social Network identity, including your public picture, may be associated with your location data. This means that the Mobile Roadie customer will be able to identify you personally and see specific locations that you have recently visited, including, potentially, your real time location, and may decide to contact you, for instance, by informing you about events or product offerings available in your area. You may at any time turn off this functionality by using the in-app privacy settings. 

Mobile Roadie Customers can also create and manage a Mobile Site via our Service without paying a fee to Mobile Roadie to do so (each a “Free Mobile Website Solution”). In the event that you use a Free Mobile Website Solution, Mobile Roadie will collect and store any personally identifiable information that you provide via the Free Mobile Website Solution, such as your name, email address, phone number, location and other optional information that we may choose to collect. This optional information is not required to use the Free Mobile Website Solution. We may use your personally identifiable information collected in these instances to contact you with information that may be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive such information from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. In the event that a Mobile Roadie Customer converts its Free Mobile Website Solution to one for which the customer must pay a fee to provide via our Service, the personally identifiable information and other information retained by Mobile Roadie prior to the date of conversion (“Specific Shared Data”), will be shared with the Mobile Roadie Customer for use by such customer to provide you with information and marketing materials about its own products and services. We only share Specific Shared Data with a Mobile Roadie Customer pursuant to an agreement under which such customer is obligated to maintain and use the Specific Shared Data it receives solely in compliance with the Mobile Roadie Privacy Policy. After conversion of the Free Mobile Website Solution to a paid Mobile Site, information collected from you via the website will be done so by Mobile Roadie on behalf of the Mobile Roadie Customer as described herein. 

On behalf of Mobile Roadie Customers, we may also collect your IP addresses as well as non-identifying details such as the geographic location of the IP address you are using to access the Internet. 

When you use a Mobile Offering , you may allow other End Users to send you personal messages, in which case we may send you alerts when you get a new message. You may at any time turn off this functionality by using the in-app privacy settings. 

You may be asked by Mobile Roadie Customers to provide additional information to them, including your personally identifiable information, to be used and shared pursuant to their own privacy policies. We encourage you to read such privacy policies before providing any information to any Mobile Roadie Customers or other third parties. While working with reputable customers is a top priority for us, we are not responsible for the use of your information by Mobile Roadie Customers, and disclaim any liability related thereto. 

**How we use your personal data?**

We use the above information in the following ways: 

  * To give ability for customers to provide services for you, using Mobile Roadie applications; 
  * To ensure that MR services are presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other device from which you access MR services; 
  * To give ability for customers to provide you with information, products or services that you request from them and which they feel may interest you - in particular, they may send you newsletters or emails. 

We do not sell any personally identifiable information of End Users to any third parties. The instances where we may share such information with third parties are described in part (D) below. 

**How you can access, update or delete your data**

You may review and update the personally identifiable information in your registration profile by logging in and editing such information in your “Settings” menu. If you decide to delete all of your personal information we may cancel your account. You shall send a request to [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com) to initiate the removal of your personal data. The request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements. 

Also, you have the right to receive a copy of certain personal information we process about you. This comprises any personal information we process on the basis of your consent. You have the right to receive this information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. You also have the right to request that we transfer that personal information to another party. You may contact us at [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com) to initiate the preparation process of a copy of your personal data. 

If you wish for us to transfer such personal information to a third party, please ensure you detail that party in your request. Note that we can only do so where it is technically feasible. Please note that we may not be able to provide you with personal information if providing it would interfere with another's rights (e.g., where providing the personal information we hold about you would reveal information about another person or our trade secrets or intellectual property). 

**Advertisement links**

The Mobile Offerings may contain links to other websites. Such websites may use cookies and/or other data collection tools. Mobile Roadie is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or the content of such websites. Mobile Roadie encourages you to read the posted privacy policies whenever interacting with any website to learn more about the privacy practices of that website. Mobile Roadie has no control over the use of your personally identifiable information by third party websites, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personally identifiable information. Additionally, Mobile Roadie does not have access to, or control of, the cookies and/or other data collection tools that may be placed on any advertisement by a third party, including those of our Mobile Roadie Customers, and this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and/or other data collection tools by any third party. 

**Your California Privacy Rights:**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits End Users who are California residents to request certain information regarding Mobile Roadie's disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [support@manageapps.net](mailto:support@manageapps.net). 

## (C) Visitors

This section describes the information that we may collect from Visitors. To the extent you are a Mobile Roadie Customer or an End User and visit the Site, this section will apply to you as well. 

**What personal information do we collect?**

If you contact us by email or by filling-out a registration form, we may keep the following information you provided: your name, company name, email address, phone number and country. 

When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's IP address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Site's technical administration, to increase our Site's functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors' needs. 

Like many websites, we may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and the Service. In addition, please be aware that other parties may also place their own cookies on the Site, and may collect or solicit personal information from you. A session cookie enables certain features of the Sites and the Service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Sites. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. As described above, most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

**How we use your personal data?**

We may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you. In addition, we may use the personal information described above to send you information regarding the Sites and/or the Service. 

**How you can delete your data**

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, email us at [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com) and request to be removed from our list. 

## (D) General

The following provisions apply to everybody (Mobile Roadie Customers, End Users and Visitors). 

**Additional information, we collect**

Cookies and similar technologies on our websites and our mobile applications allow us to track your browsing behavior, links clicked, items purchased, your device type, and to collect various data, including analytics, about how you use and interact with our Services. This allows us to provide you with more relevant product offerings, a better experience on our sites and mobile applications, and to collect, analyze and improve the performance of our Services. 

We may also collect non-Personal Data from your mobile device if you access the MR Services from your mobile device. This information is generally used to help us deliver the most relevant information to you. Examples of information that may be collected and used include information about the type of device you use. In addition, if the MR Service crashes on your mobile device, we may receive information about your mobile device model software version and device carrier, which allows us to identify and fix bugs and otherwise improve the performance of the service. This information is sent to us as aggregated information and cannot be used to identify an individual. 

**Sharing**

We may share and/or disclose information that we collect from Mobile Roadie Customers, End Users and Visitors in the following instances: 

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information. We may share aggregated information that does not include personally identifiable information and we may otherwise disclose non-identifying information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. 

Service Providers. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Site and Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to information that we collect from Mobile Roadie Customers, End Users and Visitors only to perform these tasks on our behalf. 

Business Transfers. Mobile Roadie may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including personally identifiable information collected from Mobile Roadie Customers, End Users and Visitors, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. Mobile Roadie cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information collected from Mobile Roadie Customers, End Users and Visitors to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Mobile Roadie or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

**How we secure, store and retain your data**

Mobile Roadie is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the personal data we collect, both during transmission and once received and stored, including utilization of encryption where appropriate. 

We retain personal data only for as long as necessary to provide the Services you have requested and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes. These might include retention periods: 

  * mandated by law, contract or similar obligations applicable to our business operations; 
  * for preserving, resolving, defending or enforcing our legal/contractual rights; 
  * needed to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records. 

If you have any questions about the security or retention of your personal data, you can contact us at [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com). 

**International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Mobile Roadie transfers personally identifiable information to the United States and processes it there. Whether you are a Mobile Roadie Customer, an End-User or a Visitor, your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

**Our Policy Toward Children**

Neither this Site nor the Service is directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete such information from our files. 

**Beacon Partners**

We share data we collect about you including unique identification numbers associated with mobile devices or through its API (including, for example, a Unique ID for Advertisers ("IDFA"), Unique ID for Vendors ("IDFV"), Google Ad ID, or Windows Advertising ID), mobile carrier, device type, model and manufacturer, mobile device operating system brand and model, and, depending on the user's mobile device settings and consent, the geographical location data, including GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of the mobile device (“User Data”) with our third party partners, that enables us to use Bluetooth beacons to provide you with information or offers specific to your location and interests. 

By using our Service and installing Apps containing our Signal360 integration, you give the App permission to access your device's microphone while our App is running (including while running in the background). The microphone is used as part of Signal360's PMT by detecting Beacons which emit a high frequency audio signal that cannot be heard by humans. All audio data received by the App is stored for a short time in the device's transient buffer memory which is constantly being deleted and overwritten with newer audio data. The length of the audio data stored in transient buffer memory at any given time before it is overwritten with newer audio data is up to one millisecond. None of the audio data received by the App is retained by or transmitted from your device to Signal360 servers, Beacons, or any other device. The App scans the audio data received by your device's microphone for the high frequency signal emitted by the Beacon and discards the audio data of all other frequencies. As described above, the non-discarded high frequency data is only stored in increments of up to one millisecond and is subsequently overwritten by new high frequency data in one millisecond increments. When the App detects a Beacon, it may match the signal with a set of marketing materials on your device. All marketing materials are pre-downloaded to the App as part of its regular update process. No marketing materials are sent to your device by the Beacons themselves. To put plainly: Our App does not at any time store more than up to one millisecond of your microphone's surrounding audio data; (ii) our Technology then filters and uses only the high frequency wavelengths (not audible to the human ear) of the audio data it stores for our Services; (iii) our App does not transmit any of the audio data it captures outside of your phone (neither to our servers or to any third party servers); and (iv) all audio data captured by our App is deleted and overwritten in up to one millisecond increments. 

By accepting our terms of service, you consent to the collection, storage and processing the aforementioned data by our third party partners for the purposes of: (i) providing or improving their services; (ii) enabling third parties to assist us and the retailer and venues (in which the beacons are located) in better serving and understanding our users; and (iii) sharing your data with third parties so they can provide or enable the provision of content, offers or other marketing solutions that may be of interest to you. You also consent to having your data transferred to and processed in the United States or any other jurisdiction in which our third party partners or their parent, subsidiaries, affiliates, service providers or partners maintain facilities. If you do not consent to the collection and transfer of the aforementioned data through the identification of your mobile device, we recommend that you: (a) delete our app or adjust the in-app settings of the app; or (b) delete the applicable mobile advertiser ID by limiting ad tracking on the device. For iOS, navigate to your Settings > Select Privacy > Select Advertising > Enable the “Limit Ad Tracking” setting. For Android, open your Google Settings app > Ads > Enable “Opt out of interest-based advertising". 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@mobileroadie.com](mailto:support@mobileroadie.com).
